{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"6539/17",
			"answer":"6539/17",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2414/16",
			"answer":"2414/16",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2307/99",
			"answer":"2307/99",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3401/61",
			"answer":"3401/61",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7714/22",
			"answer":"7714/22",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4.424/0.56",
			"answer":"4.424/0.56",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"13.95/3.1",
			"answer":"13.95/3.1",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"78.02/0.83",
			"answer":"78.02/0.83",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2160/2.4",
			"answer":"2160/2.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6.56/1.6",
			"answer":"6.56/1.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2307/99",
			"answer":"2307/99",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}